Guide to the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Subject Files, 1963-present UPG.RG.52
ULS Greensburg
- Gimbel Pennsylvania Art Collection, 1958-1988 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 6, Box 5, Map-case 1)
  In 1946, Gimbel Brothers, Inc., commissioned a group of American artists to create an art collection of 115 works in oil, tempera, watercolor and charcoal. In 1959, 48 paintings which depicted the city of Pittsburgh and Western Pennsylvania were given to the University of Pittsburgh. After an inaugural exhibition of the paintings in March, 1959 in the Student Union, the paintings were placed, at various times, in buildings, on the Oakland, Johnstown, and Greensburg campuses. The 1986/87 exhibition reassembled the collection from the various campuses for display at the Westmoreland Museum of Art and the University Gallery of the University of Pittsburgh.
  File contains: correspondence in re the Gimbel Pa. Art Collection for the period 1958-1964 with some correspondence extending into 1975; correspondence and memoranda in re the Gimbel Pa. Art Collection Exhibition, 1985-1990; appraisals, 1981-1986, includes inventories giving location of items at various times; invitation to reception and preview of the exhibition; program for the reception, preview and dinner at the opening of the exhibition (includes guest list, program, dinner menu); remarks of UPG President George F. Chambers at the dinner opening the exhibition; poster announcing the exhibition; photographs of the exhibition catalog plates (black/white, 44 items; color, 44 items; color negatives, 44 items; slides, 44 items); exhibition catalog, Gimbel Pennsylvania Art Collection. Exhibition Catalog. An Exhibition Co-Sponsored by the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg and Westmoreland Museum of Art. 18 October--1986--November 16. University Art Gallery, University of Pittsburgh, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania 9 January--1987--February 15. (12 copies); exhibition account; news clippings. [N.B.: 2 Copies of Exhibition Poster Housed in UPG Archives Map Cabinet]
- "Give a Thread" Clothing Drive [Give a Thread Campaign], 2014-2015 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
- Graduating Military, 2016-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
  2016 Alexander Bittner, Sean Forbis, Ashley Lewandowski, Yu Lin, Matthew Williamson, Eric Bosack 2017 Adam Elatrache, Austin Lonzo, Haleigh Morrison, Anthony Salvio, Amanda Jayasinghe 2018 Daniel Petrovay, Sarah Treadway, Jeremy Voich 2019 Brendan Conte, Rachel Grasee, John P. Ritchey, Vincent Salvio, Tyler Wellek, Demontaye Williamson
- Green Scholar Program, 2009-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
  "Established in fall 2009 the Green Scholar Program selects the best and brightest students in each of three academic divisions to work collaboratively with faculty doing research. The program allows students to expand their understanding of the majors while earning stipends as research assistants working with faculty members on specific scholarly projects. $10,000 grant from the Buncher Family Foundation supports the program."
  2009-2010 [First Green Scholars at UPG]: Deidre Stuffer, Sam Tokich
  2010-2011 Green Scholars: Nicholas Marrone, Elliot Sheedy, Deidre Stuffer, Jian Tan.
  2011-2012 Green Scholars: Brittany Kulcsar, Joseph Saccamago, Elliot Sheedy, Matthew Walko
  2012-2013 Green Scholars: Thomas K. Crowley, Brett Demarco, Donna Dineley, Megan Hughes, Ryan S. Jakubek, Karlee Sypherd
  2013-2014 Green Scholars: Sierrah Avant, Chelsea Divella, Megan Hughes, Nathan LaSor, Brittany Playso, Emily Stark, Mary Toland, James Weir
  2014-2015 Sarah Heggenstaller, Kaylynn McKinney, Luke Metzler, Lilliana Newmeyer, Rebecca Parker, Shannon Sankey, Emily Stark
  2015/2016 Adam Balliet, Stephanie Costabile, Cletus McConville, Luke Metzler, Rebecca Parker, Anna Yates
  2016/2017 Brandin Adams, Adam Balliet, Madison Bredice, Stephanie Costabile, Jonathan Horanic, Lauren McGuigan, Samantha McGuigan, Brooke Stewart, Jeremy Voich
  2017/2018 Brandin Adams, Madison Bredice, Kanita Esmeralda, Alex Fell, Jonathan Horanic, Timothy Legenzoff, Brooke Stewart
  2018/2019 Jonah Jankovik, Dorothea Lint, Sarah Rossi, Taroniar Sevathas
- Greensburg American Opera (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
- Greensburg Area Cultural Council (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
- Greensburg Bicentennial (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
  UPG is a member of this organization.
- Guanajuato Exchange Program [University of Guanajuato Exchange Program], 2000-2008 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
  Formal agreement creating an exchange agreement signed July 20, 2000.
  Prof. Juan Rene Segura, 1st Visiting Professor, Spring 2000 Term
  Reuben Alfonso Lopez Nieto, 2nd Visiting Professor, Spring 2004 Term
  Dr. Juan Pascual Gay, 3rd Visiting Professor, Spring 2007 Term
  Acta Universitaria [revista cientifica da la Universidad de Guanajuato...] 4 Issues: v. 17 #3, Sept.-Dic., 2007; v. 18, #1, Enero-Abril, 2008; v, 18 Numero Especial #1; v. 18 Supp, 2008
  See: UPG.RG.51 Biographical File; See: UPG.RG.60 Prints—Juan Segura -- Reception, 1/25/00
  See: UPG.RG.51 Biographical File; RG60 Prints – Reuben Alfonso Lopez Nieto – Reception, 4/2/04
  See: UPG.RG.51 Biographical File; Dr. Juan Pascual Gay
- Guy Rossetti International Study Endowment (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 3)
  See Also: UPG.RG.51 Biographical File – Rossetti, Dr. Guy
  UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Cultura (La) The Life and Times of Leonardo da Vinci
  UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Da Vinci Scholars
  UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Rossetti House
  UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Ser.: Prints. Cultura (La)
- Headstart Christmas Party (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 7)
- Helen Conors Psychology Prize, 2010-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 7)
  2010 Lan Liu 2011 Jennifer M. Watson, senior and Psi Chi president 2012 Lauren A. Mannella 2013 Vanessa Malinowski 2014 Sara Hoover 2015 Pamela Skovira 2016 Kelli Wilson 2017 Haleigh Morrison 2018 Rebecca Robinson, Autumn Tinta 2019 Kathleen Price
- Helen Wirsing Collection (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 7)
- High School Media Competition, 2010 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 7)
  1st annual, 2010
- Homecoming [Blue & Gold Weekend], 1999-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 7)
  1st UPG Homecoming Weekend, Sept. 24-26, 1999. 1999 Homecoming King: Sal Molitierno; Homecoming Queen: Brandy Valentine.
  Homecoming 2000. Sept. 22-24, 2000. Homecoming King: Jason Wagoner; Homecoming Queen: Beth Marr
  Homecoming 2001. Sept. 29, 2001. Homecoming King: Jamal Woodson; Homecoming Queen: Andrea Doner
  Homecoming 2010. Feb. 5-6, 2010. Homecoming King: Joel Gallucci. Homecoming Queen: Hillary Remmick
  Homecoming 2011. Sept. 30-Oct. 2, 2011. [First Annual Blue & Gold Weekend] Homecoming King: John Paul "JP" Hilzendeger; Homecoming Queen: Megan Edge.
  See also: RG60 Prints--Homecoming
  Homecoming 2012. Oct. 12-13, 2012. Homecoming King: Josh Myers. Homecoming Queen: Heather Metro.
  Homecoming 2013. Oct. 2-6.
  Homecoming 2014. Oct. 3-5. Homecoming King, Justin Marin; Homecoming Queen, Danielle Schick.
  Homecoming 2015. Oct. 2-4.
  Homecoming 2016. Sept. 30, Oct. 1-2. Homecoming King, Joe Ferrante; Homecoming Queen, Bella Smith.
  Homecoming 2017. Oct. 13-21.
  Homecoming 2018, Oct. 10-21.
- Honors Convocation, 1999-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 5, Box 7)
  1999, March 3 (1st) 2000, March 1 (2nd) 2001, March 21 (3rd) 2002, April 5 (4th) 2003, March 28 (5th) 2004, March 26 (6th) 2005, March 18 (7th) 2006, March 31 (8th) 2007, March 23 (9th) 2008, March 28 (10th) 2009, March 27 (11th) 2010, April 9, (12th) 2011, April 8 (13th) 2012, April 13 (14th) 2013, April 12 (15th) 2014, April 11 (16th) 2015, April 10 (17th) 2016, April 15 (18th) 2017, April 7 (19th) 2018, April 13 (20th) 2019, April 12 (21st) 2022, April 8 (24th) 2023, April 14 (25th) 2024, April 12 (26th)
- Honors Convocation [Pittsburgh Oakland Campus], 2000-2017 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 1)
  2000, Feb. 28 2002, Feb. 28 2005, Feb. 28 2006, Feb. 24 2008, Feb. 29 2009, Feb. 27 2013, Feb. 22 2014, Feb. 28 2015, Feb. 28 2016, Feb. 26 2017, Feb. 24
- Humanities Academic Village (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 1)
- Institute for Continued Learning, 1998-2010 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  See plan file cabinet for oversize poster: UPG.fRG.52 Subject Files--Institute for Continued Learning.
  Initiated in Fall, 1998 with first sessions taking place on Oct. 24, 31, 1998; suspended in Jan., 2001 although a final program was held in conjunction with the Elderhostel Institute Network in Mar. 2001.
  Institute resumed activities with May 5, 2009 program "The Effects of Mass Media and New Technology on Society".
  n.b.: Changed name March 15, 2010 to Center for Professional Growth at Pitt-Greensburg (CPG at UPG)
- Institutional Benchmark Report [National Survey of Student Engagement], 2001-2003 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  2001 University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus
  2002 University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus
  2003 University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus
- "Into the Streets" (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
- IPEDS [The Integrated Postsecondary Education Data System], 2007-2009 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  IPEDS Data Feedback Report, 2007. University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg
  IPEDS Data Feedback Report, 2009. University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg
- Jessica A. Drayer Chemistry Award, 2011-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  2011 Kayley Fishel 2012 Brittany Kulscar 2013 Zachary Weisner 2014 Chelsea DiVella 2016 Alexa Martin 2017 Michelle Lofink, Michael Jacobyansky 2018 Morgan Ungerleider 2019 Sarah Rossi
- Joan C. Zaleskiewicz Music Scholarship Award, 2018-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  2018 Katie Giblin 2019 Jenna Maroadi
- Joan C. Zaleskiewicz Music Service Award, 2003-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  2003 Brandon Von Bon 2005 Kyle Metzger 2006 Nicholas P. Rogers 2007 Meghan Kyle 2008 Courtney E. Hill 2009 Meghan Kyle 2010 Angela Moody 2011 Melissa Raichel 2012 Alicia DiPaolo 2013 Anthony Puzzini 2014 Alicia DiPaolo 2015 Alexander Bittner; Emily Stark 2016 Alyssa McDonald; Kaitlyn Satterfield 2017 Allison Brekosky; Miranda Smith 2018 Megan Ng 2019 Madeline Jackson
- Joan C. Zaleskiewicz Chorale Scholarship, 2012-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  [n.b.: listing only: no File Folder]
  2012 Bethany Thomas 2013 Kayla Turco 2014 Shannon Lieu 2018 Katie Giblin
- Joan Chambers Concert Series, March 1, 2008 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  Inaugural Performance, March 1, 2008
- Katz Immersion MBA Program, 1994-1996, 2009-2010 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  1994-1996, 2009-2010 1FF
  The file contains, for the 1994-1996 period, background documents (including Proposals, Surveys, notice of a Reception Dinner Meeting (with a list of dinner attendees, Memoranda, Letter) which depict an early effort to establish an MBA Program at the UPG Campus. There is a hiatus in the records between the years 1996 and 2009. In an Apr. 16, 2009 News Release the UPG Office of Institutional Advancement announced that the Univ. of Pittsburgh Joseph M. Katz Graduate School of Busines and Pitt-Greensburg teamed to offer a new Katz Immersion MBA (KIMBA) program at the UPG Campus beginning September 2009. After an unsucessful recruitment effort, the proposed Katz Immersion MBA Program at the UPG Campus was canceled in 2010. (News article, Tri. Rev., 12/28/2010, p B1,2).
- Kenneth E. Bell Nature Trail (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  See also: UPG.RG.35 UPG Senate Ser.: Subject Files. Kenneth E. Bell Memorial Fund (1974-1976); UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Programs [Dedication; Groundbreaking] Kenneth E. Bell Memorial Trail
- King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther, A Birthday Celebration for, January 15, 2008 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  1st, Jan. 15, 2008
  For prints, See: UPG.RG.60 Prints--King, Jr., Dr. Martin Luther, A Birthday Celebration For
- Latin American Studies (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
- Lavender Graduation Ceremony, 2024-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  Scope and Contents
  2024, April 25 (William Pitt Union)
- Leadership Student Recognition Awards Ceremony [Formerly Student Leadership Recognition Awards Ceremony; Leadership Recognition Awards Banquet] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  For photographs, See also UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Prints--Leadership Recognition Awards; See also UPG.RG.60 Visual Images—Negatives
- Literature Award [Junior English Literature Prize; Junior Essay in Literature Prize; Essay in Literature Prize], 2003-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  2003 Laura Dziuban 2006 Alexandra Gray 2007 James Matthews 2008 Michelle Sarver 2009 Matthew Reilly 2010 [No award listed in Honors Convocation Program for 2010. faz] 2011 Alexander Miskalls 2012 Katie Pagano 2013 Kelly Stewart 2014 Luke McDermott [Junior Literature Essay Prize] 2018 Alysee Fry [Essay in Literature Prize] 2019 Maura Barron
- Littleburg Press, 2012, 2016 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 2)
  First chapbook published: Jenna Szypulski, Fully Loaded, Automatic (2012)
  See also: UPG Special Collections: GREE PS3569 Z96F84 2012
  See also: UPG Special Collections: GREE PS504.R68 2016, Route 30, Poems, Stories and Essays ed. by Michelle Boring and Lori Jakiela.
- Manufacturing Mamagement Program (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
- Maps, 1964-2015 (Map-case 1, Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  New Campus Site University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg [ca. 1964] University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg [ca. 1982] Campus Plan University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg (11-17-86) University of Pittsburgh Greensburg [1989?] University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 1997-98 (10-10-97) University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 1998-99 University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 1999-2000 (5-18-99) University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 1999-2000r University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 2000-2001 University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 2001-2002(R1) University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 2001-2002(R2) University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 2002-2003 University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 2003-2004 University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 2004-2005 University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 2005-2006 University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 2006-2007 University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 2007-2008 University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map Rev. 10-10 University of Pittsburgh Greensburg Campus Map 2014-2015
  See also: UPG.RG.53 Maps [filed in Map Case]
- March of Dimes College Walk [March of Dimes Walk-America] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
- Mascot [UPG Mascot] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  See Also: UPG.RG.60 Prints--Mascot [UPG Mascot]
- Men Against Sexual Violence [MASV] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
- Microscopy and Digital Imaging Lab (MDL), 2016 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  Historical note: Established in 2016 with a grant from the Eberly Foundation, along with additional funding from the Richard King Mellon Foundation and Pitt-Greensburg.
- Mrs. Pennsylvania United States Pageant (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
- Music at Pitt-Greensburg, 2009-2018 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  2009/2010 2010/2011 2012/2013 2013/2014 2014/2015 2015/2016 2016/2017 2017/2018
- Nancy Estrada Mentoring Award, 2018-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  2018 George Panagis 2019 Corrine Silvio
- Natural Sciences and New Technologies [Academic] Village, September 2000 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  Formally launched Sept. 2000; Dr. Kerry Holzworth, first director. Dr. Jay Apt, former astronaut and crew member of the NASA shuttles Atlantis and Endeavour, lectured and presented a slide show titled, "This View of Earth".
  See also: UPG.RG.50 Ser.: Serials. The Lyceum Times. See also: UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Posters
- Norman McWhinney Scholarship for Excellence in Written Communication Award, 2006-2010 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  2006 Jamie Mathews; Amy Duli
  2008 Jamie Mathews; Michelle Sarver
  2009 Kalley Burtnett; Deidre Stuffer
  2010 Deidre Stuffer; Corey Florindi
  See also: UPG.RG.57 Faculty Papers. McWhinney, Dr. Norman N.
- Nursing Program, 2017-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  [4 year bachelor of science nursing program to begin Fall Term 2017/2018] White Coat Ceremony, University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg. [Program] 2018, August 29. [News Release 8/27/2019] "White Coat" Ceremony To Be Held at Pitt-Greensburg Second-Year Nursing Students to Recieve White Lab Coats "Redstone Highlands Creates Unique Nursing Scholarship" [2019]
- One Book, One Community Program [Regional Reading Project] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
- Pageant [Miss UPG Pageant: UPG Pageant; Mr. and Miss UPG Pageant] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
- PARK(ing) Day, September 20, 2019 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
- 'Partners in Excellence' Annual Internal Campaign, 2005-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  2005/2006, 2006/2007, 2015/2016, 2016/2017, 2017/2018, 2018/2019
- Peer Group Advisors [UPG Peer Group Advisors; UPG Peer Leaders] (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  See also: UPG.RG.60 Ser.: Prints – Portraits – UPG Peer Group Advisors
- Piano/Voice Studio Class (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
- Pitt Day in Harrisburg, 2011-2018 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  2011, 2012, 2015, 2016, 2018
- Pitt Day of Giving [Pitt-Greensburg's Participation], 2018-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  2018 2019 2020
- Pitt-Greensburg Cultural Series, 1997-1998 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  The Vira I. Heinz and the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg. 1997-1998: Salsamba of the Pittsburgh Jazz Society. Oct. 6, 1997. Kuntu Repertory Theatre. Feb. 10, 1998.
- Pitt-Greensburg Education Department [Program] [Pitt-Greensburg's Education Program], 2010-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  Established 2010. First graduates of the program will accept their diplomas at Commencement on April 26, 2014.
- Pitt-Greensburg Golf Outing (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
- Pitt-Greensburg Relay for Life, 2017-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  1st, 2017; 2nd, 2018; [3rd] 2019
- "Pitt Pat" Award Program, October 2000 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 3)
  "Pitt Pat" Award Program replaced by "YOU Make The Difference" Recognition Program for Univ. of Pgh. at Greensburg Staff in Oct., 2000.
- Posters, 1990-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 4)
  See also UPG.RG.52 Subject Files--Behavioral Sciences Academic Village; Humanities Academic Village; Natural Sciences and New Technologies Academic Village; Academic Villages; Rossetti International House. [Pre Aug. 2000 material may be found in these files.] See also: UPG.qRG.52 Subject Files--Posters. The University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg. [early 1990's] See also: UPG.qRG.52 Subject Files--Posters. One Book, One Community Program. 2006.
  Announcements of campus events and activities sponsored by the Rossetti International House, Humanities Academic Village, Behavioral Science Academic Village, Natural Sciences and New Technologies Academic Village and other campus organizations, clubs, and groups.
  Holdings: 3 File Folders 2000, Aug.-Dec. 2001, Jan.-Apr. 2003 (1 item)
  2005-2006, 2008, 2016, 2019
- Presidential Citation for Distinguished Service, 2002-2004 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 4)
  2002 Bryan M. Valentine 2003 Joseph A. Olcak 2004 Thomas D. Horan
- President's Advisory Committee on Diversity Affairs (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 4)
- President's Award for Staff Excellence, 1988-2006 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 4)
  [NOTE: In 2007 succeeded by President's Distinguished Service Award for Staff]
  Memorandum dtd Aug. 28, 1998 from Dr. Frank A. Cassell, Pres., in re the creation of the award; includes "Guideline"; memorandum dtd 20 Feb. 2000 in re current year's award program with enclosures of a nomination form as well as modified guidelines.
  In 1998, the President's Award for Excellence (for significant contribution to the campus demonstrated by a record of exemplary achievement during the past year) awarded to 24 faculty and staff. Faculty awardees: Vickilyn Barnot, Richard Blevins, Anthony Boldurian, Alicia Covarrubias, Nancy Estrada, Sayre Greenfield, Michael Lucci, Diane Marsh, Mark McColloch, Stephen Murabito, Mary Beth Spore, Judith Vollmer. Staff awardees: Karen Antoniak, Joyce Bucchi, Charlene Cerutti, Nancy Evans, Virginia Kemerer, Patricia LaMantia, William Martin, Richard Naccarato, Josesph Olczak, John R. Sparks, Allen Tedrow, and Charles Westbrooks. Sept. 29, 1998.
  1999, Karen Antoniak 2000, Helen Connors 2001, Janet (Dolly) Biskup 2002, Joyce Bucchi 2003, Joseph A. Olczak 2004, Parris Carter 2005, Patty LaMantia 2006, Elizabeth Tiedemann
- President's Distinguished Service Award for Staff, 2007-2016 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 4)
  [NOTE: Established under this title by Pres. Sharon P. Smith and succeeds the former President's Award for Staff Excellence.]
  2007 Awardee R. Leigh Hoffman, Assistant Dean of Student Services and Director of Orientation 2008 Awardee Michele Shuey, Academic Advisor, Office of Academic Affairs 2009 Awardee Troy Ross, Coordinator of Housing and Residence Life 2010 Awardee Cynthia Genard, Administrative Secretary, Academic Affairs 2011 Awardee Sheila Confer, Academic Village Coordinator, Part Time Instructor, Theatre Arts 2012 Awardee Lori Moore, Administrative Secretary, Human Resources 2013 Awardee Brian Root, Assistant Director of Housing and Resident Life 2014 Awardee Lisa Hope, Assistant Director for Systems Analysis 2015 Awardee Ronna Colland, Director of Business Affairs 2016 Awardees: Valerie Kubenko, Stacy Netzel
  See UPG.RG.02.5, President. Dr. Sharon P. Smith. Ser.: Memoranda. Memorandum, 15 Nov. 2007.
- President's Higher Education Community Honor Roll (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 4)
  ["...the highest federal recognition a college or university can receive for its commitment to volunteering, service-learning and civic engagement.]
- President's Medal for Distinguished Service, 1998-present (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 4)
  Inaugurated by Dr. Frank A. Cassell. First awarded in 1998.
  1998 John A. Robertshaw, Jr. 1999 No Medal Awarded 2000 Norman W. Scanlon 2000 Robert B. Van Atta 2001 Rev. Dr. Kenneth P. Rutter 2002 Millstein, Jack H., Jr. 2003 David S. Dahlman 2004 Poke, Dr. Carl A. 2004 Roach, William A. 2005 Hon. Judge John J. Driscoll 2006 Davis, Robert H. 2007 Boxx, Linda McKenna 2007 Magnuson, Ronald A. 2008 Assard, David G. 2009 Zaleskiewicz, Dr. Thad 2010 Barnot, Vicklyn, PhD 2010 Marks, Melissa J, EdD 2011 Marsh, Diane, PhD 2012 Beeson, Lillian L., PhD 2013 Kuschmierz, Ruth, PhD 2014 Whatule, Larry J., PhD 2015 McMahon, Richard B. 2016 Rossman, Jr., Carl A. 2017 Jamison, J. Wesley, PhD 2018 Wilson, Dr. Franklin David 2019 Burns, Helen K, PhD 2019 Tilstone, A. David
- President's Report to the Community [Report of President], 2000-2006 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 4)
  2000-2001, 2001-2002, 2002-2003, 2003-2004, 2005, 2006
- Programs [Dedication; Groundbreaking; Ribbon Cutting Ceremony], 1975-2012
  - Campus Clock Dedication, October 13, 1995 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Included in the file: Invitation to the dedication; Program Agenda; Remarks by Ms. Jennifer A. Borrasso, SGA President; remarks of UPG President, Dr. George F. Chambers; List of attendees.
    See UPG.RG.60 VC II. 3 for video cassette and UPG.RG.61 C 1 for audio cassette.
  - Cassell Hall [Frank A. Cassell Hall], September 5, 2012 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Ribbon-Cutting Ceremony.
    See UPG.RG.60 DVD25 for video disc of ceremony.
  - Chambers Hall, June 20, 1997 (Museum-cabinet 2, Shelf 6, Box 5)
    Renamed Chambers Hall from Common Facilities Building at renaming dedication ceremony 6/20/97.